Inventory of the F. A. Harper papers
Hoover Institution Archives
F. A. Harper papers
1876-1985
1930-1973
85025
Hoover Institution Archives
98 manuscript boxes, 6 card file boxes, 1 oversize box (40.6 linear feet)
Correspondence, speeches and writings, memoranda, reports, clippings, and other printed matter relating to laissez-faire economic and political theory, and to economic conditions and governmental economic policy in the United States.
Harper, F. A. (Floyd Arthur), 1905-1973.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1985.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Related Materials
Friedrich A. von Hayek papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Institute for Humane Studies miscellaneous records, Hoover Institution Archives
Mont Pèlerin Society records, Hoover Institution Archives
Foundation for Economic Education miscellaneous correspondence, Hoover Institution Archives
James W. Clise papers, Special Collections and University Archives, University of Oregon Libraries
Biographical Note
1905 February 7 Born, Middleville, Michigan
1926 Graduated from Michigan State University
1930 Married Marguerite Kaechele
1930-1931 Research field agent, Federal Farm Board
1932 Received Ph.D. in agricultural economics from Cornell University
1932-1946 Taught at Cornell University as an instructor and professor of marketing
1934 Business analyst, Farm Credit Association
1937 Appointed acting head of the Department of Agricultural Economics at the University of Puerto Rico
1943 Author, Inflation Is on Our Doorstep (co-authored with W.M. Curtiss)
1945 Author, The World's Hunger (co-authored with F.A. Pearson)
1946-1958 Assisted Leonard Read with founding Foundation for Economic Education (FEE) and served on its staff
1947 Attended first meeting of the Mont Pèlerin Society
1948 Author, High Prices
1949 Author, Liberty, A Path to Its Recovery
1955 Traveled to Sweden to study socialism
1957 Author, Why Wages Rise
1958-1961 Senior research economist, William Volker Fund
1961 Founded the Institute for Humane Studies
1962-1963 Visiting professor of moral philosophy, Wabash College
1962-1966 Various positions, Institute for Humane Studies
1966-1973 President, Institute for Humane Studies
1969 Author, The Crisis of the Free Market
1973 April 21 Died
1978-1979 Institute for Humane Studies publishes The Writings of F.A. Harper
Sources:
Harper, Marguerite K. "Reminiscence." The Writings of F. A. Harper, Volume 1. Menlo Park: Institute for Humane Studies, Inc., 1978. Accessed through Ludwig von Mises Institute: http://mises.org/
Koch, Charles G. "Tribute." The Writings of F. A. Harper, Volume 1. Menlo Park: Institute for Humane Studies, Inc., 1978. Accessed through Ludwig von Mises Institute: http://mises.org/
On Freedom and Free Enterprise. Ed. Mary Sennholz. New Jersy: D. Van Nostrand Company, Inc., 1956. Accessed through Ludwig von Mises Institute: http://mises.org/
Scope and Content of Collection
The papers document the career of Floyd Arthur Harper, nicknamed "Baldy," an American educator and economist who founded the Institute for Humane Studies and was a charter member of the Mont Pèlerin Society. In addition to being a fellow of the American Association for the Advancement of Science, Harper was a life fellow of the International Institute of Arts & Letters in Switzerland. In a memorial to Harper, Murray Rothbard wrote, "Ever since he came to the Foundation for Economic Education in 1946 as its chief economist and theoretician, Baldy Harper, in a very real sense, has been the libertarian movement. For all these years, this gentle and lovable man, this wise and Socratic teacher, has been the heart and soul and nerve center of the libertarian cause." The collection contains correspondence, speeches and writings, reports, clippings, sound recordings, and printed matter relating to laissez-faire economic and political theory, economic conditions, and governmental economic policy in the United States.
Harper grew up on a farm in Michigan, an experience that influenced his interest in agricultural economics. In 1932, he received his Ph.D. in agricultural economics from Cornell University and began his teaching career at that institution, eventually becoming a professor of marketing in the Department of Agriculture. Course materials, lectures, research and other materials from Harper's time at Cornell can be found in Boxes 91 through 94 and Box 104. From 1962 to 1963, Harper was a visiting professor of moral philosophy at Wabash College. Some of his Wabash College seminar material can be found in Box 10 and Box 52.
In addition to being an educator, Harper was a prolific author. Many of his works discuss liberty, especially in relation to free market economics. Harper's speeches and writings, which can be found in Boxes 1 to 11, Boxes 79 to 90, and elsewhere as listed, contain drafts, lectures, correspondence, notes, outlines, conference materials, clippings, and printed matter. Some of the files contain materials labeled as unpublished. Speeches from meetings of the Mont Pèlerin Society can be found in these files. For Harper's Free Enterprise Institute lectures, see Box 95. For a bibliography of Harper's works, see Box 4 and Box 49. In 1955, Harper traveled to Sweden to study socialism and its effects on the Swedish people. With Frank B. Keith, Harper compiled a Swedish-English glossary of social science terms. This glossary, materials concerning his study, and the subject file on Sweden can be found in Boxes 53, 79, and 99 through 102.
In 1961, Harper founded the Institute for Humane Studies (IHS), an organization dedicated to research in the humane scholarly disciplines, with a council of advisors that included Friedrich A. von Hayek, Ludwig von Mises, and Murray N. Rothbard and a board of directors that included Charles G. Koch. Much of the correspondence found in the collection is from the time period when Harper worked for the William Volker Fund and the Institute of Humane Studies. The majority of the correspondence, left in the order it was received, is arranged in two alphabetical lists by name of correspondent, organization, or project. Many of the letters received after 1973 are address updates for the IHS mailing list (Boxes 60-78).
Harper created the Harper System for Libraries and Files, which he used to organize his own subject files. In his subject files, individual clippings and other subject materials are numbered based on date of acquisition, with items acquired most recently taking the next available number. Although most of Harper's files follow this rule, it appears the files do contain interfiles, so that some later materials can be found with earlier materials of the same subject. In these cases and other situations where multiple documents have been grouped together by subject, several documents have the same number attached to them. A card file accompanies these items, listing subjects, authors, and other access points, then the name of the document and number assigned by Harper. The card file for Harper's subject files can be found in Boxes 54 through 56. For more information about this system, see "Harper System for Libraries and Files" (Box 13 and Box 81).
Harper's subject files contain clippings, printed matter, excerpts, correspondence, notes, quotations, and writings by Harper and others. Subject materials for the White House Conference on Aging can be found at number 3146. Papers delivered at the 9th meeting of the Mont Pèlerin Society are filed under 3425 to 3428, while a lecture by Karl Popper can be found under number 3753. Most of the earlier materials in the subject files, such as materials from the 1800s, are photocopies or transcriptions, not original documents. There are a few instances of photocopies of works published in the 1700s. For common subjects found in the subject file, see the list below.
The majority of the collection remains in the order it was received, except for moving sound recordings in Box 105 and sorting of various folders for use.
Common Subjects in Harper's Subject File
To access the content, look up the subject term in the card file (Boxes 54-56, 102), note the numbers on the cards, and consult the files for those numbers (Boxes 13-49).
Academic freedom
Agriculture
Agricultural relief
Anarchy
Anti-trust
Authority
Bastiat, Frédéric
Bibliography
Britain
Business cycle (and fluctuations)
Capital
Capital formation
Capitalism
Censorship
Charity
Christianity
Churches
Civil rights
Clark, Colin
Closed shop
Colleges and universities
Communism
Competition
Conscription
Cooperation
Corporations
Creative thinking
Credit
Crime
Cycles
Debt
Democracy
Discovery
Discrimination
Economics
Education
Education, Federal aid for
Energy
Families
Federal Reserve
Foreign aid
FEE (Foundation for Economic Education)
France
Freedom
Friedman, Milton
Germany
Gold
Government
Government costs
Government debt
Government, proper role of
Harper, F. A. publications (includes biographical material)
Hayek, F. A.
Health insurance, public
History
Human rights
Incentives
Income
Income distribution
Income tax
Individualism
Inflation
Insurance
Interest rates
Keynes, John Maynard
King, Willford I.
Labor unions
Language
Law
Liberalism
Liberty
Management
Marx, Karl (and Marxism)
Military training
Mises, Ludwig von
Money
Monopoly
Mont Pèlerin Society
Morals
National income
Natural law
Negroes and Negro problems (see also Don Warden file in Box 51)
Organizations
Parks, Mercer H.
Peace
Philosophy
Politics
Population
Power
Price control
Prices
Principle
Productivity
Profits
Property rights
Read, Leonard E.
Rebellion
Religion
Research
Revolution
Rothbard, Murray
Russia
Savings
Science
Single tax
Slavery
Social science
Social security
Socialism
Sorokin, Pitirim A.
Subsidies
Sweden
Tariffs
Taxes and taxation
Unemployment
United Nations
Variation
Volker Fund
Wage rates
War
Wealth
Welfare
World government
Economics.; Free enterprise.; Liberty.; United States--Economic conditions.; Economists.; Institute for Humane Studies.
- Speeches and writings by Harper, 1951-1972 (Box 1)
- Speeches and writings by Harper, clippings, 1967-1973 (Box 2)
- Charts and transparencies, 1951-1956, undated (Box 2)
- Project files, 1961-1967 (Box 2)
- White House Conference on Aging, 1960 (Box 2)
- Charts and transparencies, 1950s-1970s, undated (Box 3)
- Bibliographies, 1950-1967 (Box 4)
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes list of Harper's publications.
- Charts, 1964, undated (Box 4)
- Speeches and writings by Harper (Boxes 4-9)
  - 1965-1974 (Box 4)
  - 1958-1964, undated (Box 5)
  - 1956-1957 (Box 6)
  - 1949-1955 (Box 7)
  - 1941-1949 (Box 8)
  - 1931-1940 (Box 9)
- Excerpts from lectures by Bruno Leoni before the Fellows of the Freedom School Phrontistery, 1963-1964 (Box 9)
- War and peace subject files, 1950-1965 (Box 9)
- Speeches and writings by Harper, 1949 (Box 10)
- Reviews of Wabash College Seminars taught by Harper, circa 1962-1963 (Box 10)
- Speeches and writings by Harper, circa 1945-1971 (Box 11)
  Contains files on Why Wages Rise.
- Clippings, 1966-1972 (Box 11)
- Writings by others, 1969-1970 (Box 11)
- Peace and War Project, undated (Box 11)
- Subject files, unnumbered, 1953-1973 (Box 12)
- Survey results, outstanding persons in libertarian education, 1961 (Box 12)
- Speeches and writings by Harper, 1947-1972 (Box 13)
  Includes unpublished essays.
- Subject files, 1876-1973 (bulk 1940s-1970s), undated (Boxes 13-49)
  See also: card file in Boxes 54 through 56. Majority of material in 1700s, 1800s, and early 1900s is photocopied or transcribed, not original documents.
  - 1 to 95 (Box 13)
  - 96 to 184 (Box 14)
  - 185 to 317 (Box 15)
  - 318 to 468 (Box 16)
  - 469 to 615 (Box 17)
  - 616 to 806 (Box 18)
  - 807 to 960 (Box 19)
  - 961 to 1157 (Box 20)
  - 1158 to 1311 (Box 21)
  - 1312 to 1446 (Box 22)
  - 1447 to 1562 (Box 23)
  - 1563 to 1691 (Box 24)
  - 1692 to 1808 (Box 25)
  - 1809 to 2012 (Box 26)
  - 2013 to 2138 (Box 27)
  - 2139 to 2196 (Box 28)
  - 2197 to 2262 (Box 29)
  - 2263 to 2321 (Box 30)
  - 2322 to 2435 (Box 31)
  - 2436 to 2544 (Box 32)
  - 2545 to 2698 (Box 33)
  - 2699 to 2771 (Box 34)
  - 2806 to 3010 (Box 35)
  - 3011 to 3060 (Box 36)
  - 3061 to 3146 (Box 37)
  - 3171 to 3296 (Box 38)
  - 3297 to 3352 (Box 39)
  - 3353 to 3360 (Box 40)
  - 3360 to 3363 (Box 41)
  - 3364 to 3438 (Box 42)
  - 3439 to 3569 (Box 43)
  - 3570 to 3663 (Box 44)
  - 3664 to 3782 (Box 45)
  - 3783 to 3965 (Box 46)
  - 3966 to 4120 (Box 47)
  - 4121 to 4245 (Box 48)
    Includes unnumbered file about gold.
  - 4246 to 4254 (Box 49)
- List of Harper publications, circa 1973 (Box 49)
- Front matter and correspondence for The Writings of F. A. Harper, 1976-1977 (Box 49)
- Speeches and writings by Harper, undated (Box 49)
- Correspondence, 1947-1970 (Box 49)
  Many letters include subject file numbers. Includes correspondence of Marguerite K. Harper.
- Inflation, money, and taxes subject file, 1948-1972 (Box 50)
  Includes documents with subject file numbers.
- Correspondence, 1946-1983 (Box 50)
  Includes correspondence of Marguerite K. Harper.
- Writings by Harper, clippings, 1967-1973 (Box 50)
- Correspondence and notes transcriptions, 1948-1970 (Box 51)
  Possibly from Institute for Humane Studies.
- Correspondence, 1970-1982 (Box 51)
  Mainly correspondence of Marguerite K. Harper.
- Don Warden file, 1964-1966 (Box 51)
- Photographs, undated (Box 51)
- Speeches and writings by Harper, printed matter, 1957-1960 (Box 52)
  Includes foreign language translations.
- Wabash College seminar reading materials, "Liberty in Human Society,", complied 1962-1963 (Box 52)
- Subject file on taxes, 1960-1973 (Box 52)
- Unfiled subject material, 1957-1971 (Box 52)
- Printed matter on Sweden, 1950-1957, undated (Box 53)
- Card file for Harper's subject file, undated (Boxes 54-56)
  See also: Box 102
- Card file, authors, undated (Box 57)
- Card file, titles, undated (Box 58)
  Includes unfiled cards.
- Card file, titles, undated (Box 59)
  Not in order
- Correspondence I (Boxes 60-66)
  See also: Boxes 66 to 78 for second alphabetical list and Box 51.
  - Abelson, Sidney, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 60: 1)
  - Ackerman, Adolph J., 1965-1968 (Box-folder 60: 2)
  - Adams, Charles F., 1968-1972 (Box-folder 60: 3)
  - Aeschliman, Richard D., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 60: 4)
  - Alger, Bruce, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 60: 5)
  - Allais, Maurice, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 60: 6)
  - Allen, Gordon M., 1969 (Box-folder 60: 7)
  - Allen, Myron S., 1968 (Box-folder 60: 8)
  - American Opinion Speakers Bureau, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 60: 9)
  - American Opinion Wholesale Books, 1973 (Box-folder 60: 10)
  - Andreen, Finn, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 60: 11)
  - Angas, L. L. B., 1959-1970 (Box-folder 60: 12)
  - Audouin, Anne, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 60: 13)
  - Augustin (J. J.) Inc. Publisher, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 60: 14)
  - Backster, Cleve, 1969 (Box-folder 60: 15)
  - Baldwin, Jack B., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 60: 16)
  - Barber, G. Russell, 1969 (Box-folder 60: 17)
    Includes attachments and notes.
  - Barradas, Gerald, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 60: 18)
  - Beck, Edward W., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 60: 19)
  - Beckwith, Sterling, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 60: 20)
  - Bielinski, W. Victor, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 60: 21)
  - Boehme, Lillian R., 1971-1973 (Box-folder 60: 22)
  - Boldyreff, C. W., 1961-1970 (Box-folder 60: 23)
  - Bradburn, Justin G., Jr., 1972 (Box-folder 60: 24)
  - Bratt, Anne Marie, 1968 (Box-folder 60: 25)
  - Bray, Richard, 1967 (Box-folder 60: 26)
  - Bregger, John, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 60: 27)
  - Broten, Paul R., 1970-1972 (Box-folder 60: 28)
  - Brown, Fabian, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 60: 29)
  - Brownlee, Thomas, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 60: 30)
  - Bruce, Glen, 1966 (Box-folder 60: 31)
  - Butz, Earl L., 1968-1970 (Box-folder 60: 32)
  - Byles, Calvin, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 60: 33)
  - Campbell, Albert M., 1961-1970 (Box-folder 60: 34)
  - Campbell, Garland L., 1965-1968 (Box-folder 60: 35)
  - Carnaghan, Robert B., 1968-1972 (Box-folder 60: 36)
  - Carto, Willis, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 60: 37)
  - Casey, William, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 60: 38)
  - Centro de Estudios Sobre la Libertad, 1966 (Box-folder 60: 39)
  - Chicago Society, 1970 (Box-folder 60: 40)
  - Clark, Gordon, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 60: 41)
  - Cline, Lee, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 60: 42)
  - Coast Federal, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 60: 43)
  - Coe Foundation, 1967 (Box-folder 60: 44)
  - Cohan, Steve, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 61: 1)
  - Cole, Thomas, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 61: 2)
  - Colson Management Project, 1968 (Box-folder 61: 3)
  - Cornell University Press, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 61: 4)
  - Corske, Mark, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 61: 5)
  - Cornell Club, 1972 (Box-folder 61: 6)
  - Cornuelle, Ralph D., 1966 (Box-folder 61: 7)
  - Cotton, Sandra, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 61: 8)
  - Cotton, Wright C., 1967-1972 (Box-folder 61: 9)
  - Coughenour, Newton M., 1963-1969 (Box-folder 61: 10)
  - Covalt, Frederick A., 1967-1969 (Box-folder 61: 11)
  - Cowdry, E. V., 1959-1975 (Box-folder 61: 12)
  - Dean, Jim, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 61: 13)
  - Deemer, Evelyn, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 61: 14)
  - De Grazia, Sebastian, 1972 (Box-folder 61: 15)
  - Dent, Ulysses R., 1971 (Box-folder 61: 16)
  - Dewey, Edward R., 1959-1971 (Box-folder 61: 17)
  - Diaz, Ramon P. (Uruguay), 1971 (Box-folder 61: 18)
  - Dick, Carl, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 61: 19)
  - Dorl, Roland T., 1968-1971 (Box-folder 61: 20)
  - Dun & Bradstreet, 1971 (Box-folder 61: 21)
  - Duncan, G. A., 1961-1973 (Box-folder 61: 22)
  - Durkee, Jackson, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 61: 23)
  - Earhart Foundation, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 61: 24)
  - Educational Television Council of Central New York, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 61: 25)
  - Ellison, A. E., 1967-1968 (Box-folder 61: 26)
  - Evans, M. Stanton, 1968 (Box-folder 61: 27)
  - Evans, William S., 1966-1971 (Box-folder 61: 28)
  - Exposition Press, Inc., 1965-1967 (Box-folder 61: 29)
  - Ferrero, Romulo A., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 61: 30)
  - Fifield, James W., Jr., 1965-1977 (Box-folder 61: 31)
  - Flach, Sixten, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 61: 32)
  - Fleming, Ward, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 61: 33)
  - Forum for Contemporary History, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 61: 34)
  - Francois, William, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 61: 35)
  - Fraser, James L., 1965-1970 (Box-folder 61: 36)
  - Freeman, Joseph F., II, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 61: 37)
  - French, C. E., 1970-1972 (Box-folder 61: 38)
  - Frickhoffer, Wolfgang, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 62: 1)
  - Furfey, Paul Hanley, 1971, 1977 (Box-folder 62: 2)
  - Gandil, Christian, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 62: 3)
  - Gatterdam, Annette Z., 1966-1969 (Box-folder 62: 4)
  - Geiger, Henry, 1964-1973 (Box-folder 62: 5)
  - Gibbs, M. M. (Morey), 1966-1970 (Box-folder 62: 6)
  - Gibson, Albert, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 62: 7)
  - Gifford, P. W., 1961-1970 (Box-folder 62: 8)
  - Gillespie, Tyrone, 1969 (Box-folder 62: 9)
  - Goldin, Kenneth D., 1970-1973 (Box-folder 62: 10)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 62: 11)
  - Gould, Laurence M., 1963-1973 (Box-folder 62: 12)
  - Graaff, A. de, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 62: 13)
  - Grantchester, Lord, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 62: 14)
  - Grebe, John J., 1965-1973 (Box-folder 62: 15)
  - Grove, Cecil, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 62: 16)
  - Hamner, John, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 62: 17)
  - Harwood, E. C., 1971 (Box-folder 62: 18)
  - Hasebroock, Margaret E., 1969 (Box-folder 62: 19)
  - Haughton, William R., 1958-1961 (Box-folder 62: 20)
  - Havard, Edward, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 62: 21)
  - Helsabeck, Fred, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 62: 22)
  - Hess, Karl, 1969 (Box-folder 62: 23)
  - Hildebrand, Earl M., 1967-1973 (Box-folder 62: 24)
  - Hirsch, Jerry, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 62: 25)
  - Hirshleifer, Jack, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 62: 26)
  - Horinouchi, Isao, 1968 (Box-folder 62: 27)
  - Hubbert, M. K., 1963-1976 (Box-folder 62: 28)
  - Hubert, John, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 62: 29)
  - Hudson, Morley A., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 62: 30)
  - Hudson, William L., 1967-1969 (Box-folder 62: 31)
  - Hughes, Earl, 1958-1971 (Box-folder 62: 32)
  - Hukari, Harvey, undated (Box-folder 62: 33)
  - Hunold, Albert, 1960-1972 (Box-folder 62: 34)
  - Ingwalson, Kenneth W., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 62: 35)
  - Ivens, Michael, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 62: 36)
  - Iwai, Yujiro, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 62: 37)
  - Jackman, Dean M., 1959-1969 (Box-folder 62: 38)
  - Jahn, William A., 1963-1970 (Box-folder 62: 39)
  - Jewkes, John, 1960-1971 (Box-folder 62: 40)
  - Johnson, Thomas F., 1960-1972 (Box-folder 62: 41)
  - Johnson, Thomas L., 1970-1972 (Box-folder 62: 42)
  - Johnston, Douglas E., 1968-1973 (Box-folder 62: 43)
  - Johnston, Henry, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 62: 44)
  - Jones, Mark M., 1967-1973 (Box-folder 62: 45)
  - Jouvenel, Bertrand de, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 62: 46)
  - Katz, Howard, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 62: 47)
  - Kershner, Howard E., 1958-1973 (Box-folder 62: 48)
  - Kidd, John L., 1968-1969 (Box-folder 62: 49)
  - King, Hugh P., 1959-1973 (Box-folder 63: 1)
  - Klein, Grace A., 1968-1973 (Box-folder 63: 2)
  - Klerk, Jack P. de, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 63: 3)
  - Knott, Walter, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 63: 4)
  - Lamb, James N., 1958-1964 (Box-folder 63: 5)
  - Leffson, Ulrich, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 63: 6)
  - Lewis, J. Dohn, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 63: 7)
  - Lhoste-Lachaume, Pierre, 1958-1972 (Box-folder 63: 8)
  - Lindsey, David E., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 63: 9)
  - McGehee, Mike, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 63: 10)
  - McGivern, Thomas, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 63: 11)
  - McNair, Lawrence N., 1970 (Box-folder 63: 12)
  - Metcalf, Robert M., Jr., 1966-1973 (Box-folder 63: 13)
  - Milam, Mobley M., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 63: 14)
  - Milione, Louis G., 1971 (Box-folder 63: 15)
  - Milliman, Jerome W., 1962-1970 (Box-folder 63: 16)
  - Moreel, Ben, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 63: 17)
  - Mullendore, W. C., 1960-1967 (Box-folder 63: 18)
  - Myers, William I., 1958-1972 (Box-folder 63: 19)
  - Muthesuis, Volkmar, 1960-1971 (Box-folder 63: 20)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1970 (Box-folder 63: 21)
  - Neill, Humphrey, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 63: 22)
  - Onstott, Howard R., 1970-1973 (Box-folder 63: 23)
  - Opitz, Edmund A., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 63: 24)
  - Orr, Cassie, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 63: 25)
  - Orvis, Clay Hardin, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 63: 26)
  - Overesch, Frederic, 1961-1972 (Box-folder 63: 27)
  - Palo Alto Times, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 63: 28)
  - Parker, Milo A., 1966-1974 (Box-folder 63: 29)
  - Parker, William R., 1971 (Box-folder 63: 30)
  - Paton, William A., 1959-1971 (Box-folder 63: 31)
  - Patrick, William P., 1966-1972 (Box-folder 63: 32)
  - Payton, Marick Dwight, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 63: 33)
  - Pease, Niles, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 63: 34)
  - Pei, Mario, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 63: 35)
  - Perekrestov, O. V., 1968-1970 (Box-folder 63: 36)
  - Peterson, Arthur, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 63: 37)
  - Peterson, Rudolph A., 1964-1967 (Box-folder 63: 38)
  - Pew, J. Howard, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 63: 39)
  - Pick, Franz, 1959-1971 (Box-folder 64: 1)
  - Il Politico, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 64: 2)
  - Popper, Karl R., 1962-1973 (Box-folder 64: 3)
  - Poremsky, V. Vladimir, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 64: 4)